<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Julien Rousé&#39;s home on Learning for fun and profits</title>
    <link>https://julienrouse.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Julien Rousé&#39;s home on Learning for fun and profits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://julienrouse.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First contribution: cl-string</title>
      <link>https://julienrouse.com/projects/contributions/cl-string/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julienrouse.com/projects/contributions/cl-string/</guid>
      <description>First contribution to another project on Github ever! :)
It was very small, the library was a very small and new library that wanted to groups lots of functionalities pertaining to strings for Common Lisp. The creator/maintener asked for help on the lisp subreddit and I gave it a try. It was a good way to get my feet wet, a very small project with a responsive maintener that took the time to explains things to me on how to contribute on Github and such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hugo-resume fix some css</title>
      <link>https://julienrouse.com/projects/contributions/hugo-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julienrouse.com/projects/contributions/hugo-resume/</guid>
      <description>It feels good to fix the theme I use for the blog, I give back to a tool I will use for some time hopefully :)
The problem was that when looking at blog post with full resolution on my laptop, it displayed nicely. But when viewing it with smartphone resolution, it looked like this:
  After some duckduckgoing, I stumbled upon box-sizing: border-box, an element I have not used before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSD1 certification post-mortem</title>
      <link>https://julienrouse.com/blog/professional-scrum-developer-certification-post-mortem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julienrouse.com/blog/professional-scrum-developer-certification-post-mortem/</guid>
      <description>Reflection on how I got my PSD1 certification and what you can learn from my success and failures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reddit bot to make a wordcloud</title>
      <link>https://julienrouse.com/projects/creations/reddit_bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julienrouse.com/projects/creations/reddit_bot/</guid>
      <description>A Reddit bot that read posts and comments from a subreddit, tokenize them and output a wordcloud. The shape of the wordcloud can be configured.
It is a very small project, was one of my first &amp;ldquo;real-world&amp;rdquo; project using a third-party API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://julienrouse.com/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julienrouse.com/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
1 2  [outputs] home = [&amp;#34;HTML&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;JSON&amp;#34;]   Searching additional fields To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>